twaitter.com 2011-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Twitter Business and Marketing Tools - twAitter.com

We have resolved the login issues. Thanks for your patience.

General Guidelines for Information Collection and Use:

Twaitter collects and compiles statistical information about all visitors to our web site, even if they haven't registered. The information used to compile statistics is passed from a visitor's computer to our server each time a page is requested. This statistical information is logged and provides long-term usage data and trends that help Twaitter allocate resources and better meet demands during peak usage. This information is not linked to the end user and is not considered personal information.  
The information collected includes:

1\. The type and version of your Operating System and Web Browser  
2\. Your computer's IP address  
3\. The date and time of your visit  
4\. What page you visited  
5\. What page you came from

When you register with Twaitter, you are no longer anonymous. Twaitter reserves the right to repost your messages and use them in accordance with the Twitter.com Terms of service agreement. Information Sharing and Disclosure

Other than the following instances, Twaitter does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with any other person(s) or organization(s):

* Twaitter may share your information with outsourced service providers in order to provide the materials you requested. For example, to fill an order for training materials, your name, address, and phone number may be provided to a third-party order filling agency so they can ship you the materials.  
* When the law requires Twaitter to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, Twaitter provides the information needed to obey the law. Twaitter also may provide information in order to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
* Twaitter believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
* Twaitter may also share your information with Partner organizations and associations. Because Twaitter is in no way responsible for the actions of their Partners, Twaitter can not be held liable for their Partners’ use (or misuse) of personal information.

Twaitter makes every reasonable effort to ensure the security of the data it collects. However, Twaitter cannot warrant against the disclosure of this information in the event of a security breach or other event beyond our control.

Cookies:

To facilitate the experience our website strives to offer, Twaitter may use cookies to store various pieces of information on your computer. The information in these cookies is only retrievable by Twaitter servers. We are confident the information within the cookies is reasonably secure. Although vulnerabilities in this technology exist, by keeping your web browser up to date, it is unlikely the information in these cookies will be misappropriated.

A cookie is a data file stored on your hard drive by your browser. It does not contain any executable code and cannot gather information from your computer that you have not already provided Twaitter either in a form, or by requesting a page from our site (see 'General Guidelines for Information Collection and Use', above).

Most browsers allow users to choose not to receive cookies. If you disable cookies on your browser, some pages on our site may not work correctly (or at all!), or some features may be disabled.

Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information:

A registered user may edit their personal account information by logging-in to Twaitter.com and clicking on the “My Workspace” link on the top right of the page, then clicking on “Account”. In “Account” Users may edit and update their personal information.

New program information may be added from time-to-time. Twaitter will attempt to anticipate your interest in this information based on information in your profile, and may sign you up automatically. You may opt-out of some of these services by editing your account information (as described above).

Twaitter reserves the right to send important announcements or notices to all registered users without extending an opportunity to opt-out of such notices.

Twaitter reserves the right to maintain archival copies of contact data of our registrants. The primary purpose of this archive is to prevent accidentally re-adding you to our service if you have requested not to receive further information. Concerns about this archival copy may be addressed to the webmaster.

Confidentiality and Security

Twaitter limits access to your personal information to those Twaitter employees who have a need to come into contact with that information.

To protect your personal information, Twaitter employs physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations.

Your personal information is password protected and, in some cases, encrypted for additional protection.

Changes to this Policy

Twaitter may update its privacy policy from time-to-time and will notify you about significant changes to its policy either by:

1\. emailing your primary e-mail address registered with us, or  
2\. prominently displaying a notice on our website.

Other Notices

On occasion, you may find links on our site that lead to pages provided by organizations other than Twaitter whose content and associated privacy policy are beyond our control. Twaitter makes every reasonable effort only to link to content it believes its patrons would approve. However, despite Twaitter' efforts, you are strongly advised to make yourself aware of any privacy policies applicable to those pages linked from Twaitter, since Twaitter cannot be held accountable for the content on, or linked to, on those linked pages.
